Finding AId to the Joseph Breck Records, 1916-1951 Archives.Breck.1 Archives.Breck.1
The Metropolitan Museum of Art Archives
- Joseph Breck Records, 1916-1951
  - Fink, Colin G., 1929 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Finlayson, Donald L., 1925 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Floor Plans., 1926 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Foote, E. T. (And Mr. Carr)., 1922-1923 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Foote, E. T., 1924-1927 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Foote, E. T. and Foster, F. M., 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Foote, E. T. and Foster, F. M., 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Forbes, Edward., 1922-1933 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Forgeries., 1933 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Foster, F. M., 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Frankel, S. W., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - French, Daniel Chester., 1918-1930 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - French, P.W., 1919-1925 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - French, P. W. & Co., 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - French, P. W. & Co., 1928-1930 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - French & Co., 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Friedley, Durr., 1923 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Friedsam, Col. Michael., 1923-1928 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Friedsam Collection., 1932 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Friedsam Collection -- 2nd Copy of List., 1932 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Friedsam Collection -- 3rd Copy of List., 1932 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - F -- Miscellaneous., 1918-1932 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Gallatin, Albert Eugene., 1924-1930 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Galleria Sangiorgi., 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Garvan, Francis P., 1918-1929 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Gash, Miss., 1921-1933 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Gifts (List of)., 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Gilling Castle., 1929 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Gnoli, Count Umberto., 1929-1932 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Godwin, Blake-More., 1926-1933 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Goldman, Henry., 1920-1926 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Goldschmidt Galleries (Julius F.)., 1922-1926 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Grancsay, Stephen., 1921-1933 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Graves, George Coe., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Graves, George Coe., 1931 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Graves, George Coe (Henry Graves Jr.)., 1932 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Greene, Nelle Da Costa (Pierpont Morgan Library)., 1918-1930 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Greenleaf, Richard C., 1923-1929 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Grier, Miss., 1926-1933 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Griffiths, Mrs. John L. (Caroline)., 1932 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Grinnell, William Milne (Bequest)., 1920 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation., 1926-1932 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Guide to Collections., 1933 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - G -- Miscellaneous., 1919-1933 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Hagedorn, Hermann., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Hague, Miss Marian., 1921-1928 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Hallowell, Robert., 1923-1931 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Halpert, Edith Gregor., 1927-1933 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Halsey, R. T. H., 1924-1932 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Harkness, Mrs. Edward S., 1931 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Harris, Lionel and Maurice., 1927-1933 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Harris, William Laurel., 1923-1924 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Harsche, Robert B., 1922-1931 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Haskell, Mrs. J. Amory., 1932 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Havemeyer Bequest., 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Havemeyer Catalogue., 1930 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hawkes, Mrs. Morris., 1922-1926 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hewitt, Conrad., 1918-1923 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hewitt, Conrad., 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hewitt, Conrad., 1927-1929 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hewitt, Conrad., 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hewitt, Eleanor G., Sarah Cooper Erskine., 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hewitt, Erskine (Estate of Sarah Cooper Hewitt)., 1931 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hitchcock, Henry Russell, Mrs. Ripley (Art Center)., 1922-1927 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Holmes, W. H., 1922-1924 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Houston, G. Sidney Jr., 1926-1929 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Howe, Winifred E., 1922-1925 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Howe, Mrs. WInifred., 1926-1929 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Howe, Winifred E., 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hudnut, Alexander., 1920-1921 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hutchinson, Charles L., 1919 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - H -- Miscellaneous (Ha-Hi)., 1924-1933 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - H -- Miscellaneous (Ho-Hy)., 1918-1933 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Information Concerning Works of Art (Memo)., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Ingram, Cornelia., 1921-1925 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Installation & Changes in Galleries & Storage Rooms (Estimates, etc.)., 1924-1933 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Instituto Italiano Rava., 1926 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Interiors (List of Types of)., 1932 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Ispinian, B. K., 1923 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Italian Renaissance Loan Exhibition., 1923 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ivins, William M., Jr., 1924-1932 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Ivories., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - I -- Miscellaneous., 1923-1933 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Jakober, Hans., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Jenkins, B. M. & T., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Francis C., 1921-1924 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Jones, The John Corporation., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - J -- Miscellaneous., 1919-1933 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "K" Wing., 1926 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Kahn, Ely Jacques (Buchman and Kahn)., 1929 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Jalebdjian Freres., 1922-1925 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Kane Bequest., 1926 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Kann, Alphonse., 1926 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Kelekian, Dikran G., 1923-1932 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Kelley, Charles Faben., 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Kent, H. W., 1918-1921 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Kent, H. W. -- Biography., 1922 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Kent. H. W., 1922 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Kent, H. W., 1923 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Kent, H. W., 1924 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Kent, H. W., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Kent, H. W., 1926 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Kent, H. W., 1927 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kent, H. W., 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Kent, H. W., 1929 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Kent, H. W., 1930 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Kent, H. W., 1931 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Kent, H. W. and G. L. Greenway., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kent, H. W. and G. L. Greenway., 1932-1933 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kessel, Dr. and Mrs. Leo., 1928-1932 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kevorkian, H., 1923-1925 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kimball, Fiske., 1929-1933 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kinderman, Walker C., 1919-1930 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kleinberger Galleries, Inc., 1918-1929 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Klotz, N. Georges., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Koechlin, Raymond., 1926-1930 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kraushaar, C. W. (Art Galleries)., 1923-1933 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kris, Dr. Ernst., 1930-1932 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kunstblatt, Das., 1931 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - K -- Miscellaneous., 1918-1932 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Laces., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Lamm, Olof H., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Leach, H. G., 1927-1930 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ledoux, Louis V., 1925-1929 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Lehman, Mrs. Philip., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Lenders (List of)., 1927 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Lenygon and Morant., 1924-1930 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Levy, B. David., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Lewisohn, Mrs. Frederick., 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Liberty Magazine., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Linzee, Anita M. (Mes. John)., 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Lists., 1922 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Lists., 1923 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - List of Important Officials of Museum., 1934-1935 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - List of Important Officials of Museum., 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Lists of Objects Recommended for Sale., 1927 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Lists of Objects Recommended for Sale (Older Copies)., 1927 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Little, Francis (Mrs. W. N.)., 1925-1933 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Loan Reports., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Loewi, Adolfo., 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Loewinthan, Albert., 1928-1933 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Lord & Taylor., 1926 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Lusk, Mrs. (Mae?)., 1927-1932 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Lythgoe, Albert M., 1922-1929 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - L -- Miscellaneous., 1918-1932 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Maag, Edward., 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Mackay, Clarence H., 1930-1933 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Maclagan, Eric., 1925-1933 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Macomber, H. P., 1922-1927 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Macy, V. Everit., 1924-1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Mallett & Son., 1929-1932 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Mandix (P.C.) Company, Inc., 1930 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Mansfield, Emily., 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Mansfield, Howard., 1918-1933 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Mantelet, R. (Vitrines)., 1925 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Marillier, H. C. (Morris & Co.)., 1923-1931 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Martinovitch, Prof. Nicholas., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Marquand, Prof. Allan., 1918-1924 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Mason, W. E., 1922-1928 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - McClellan, Hon. George B., 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - McComb, Arthur K., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - McFadden, Miss., 1931-1933 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Means, Philip Ainsworth., 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Mechlin, Leila., 1922-1928 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Meigs, Ruth Averell., 1924-1932 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Metman, L., 1929-1931 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Museum Studies., 1928 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Museum Studies., 1929 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Museum Studies., 1930-1933 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Middledorf, Dr. Ulrich., 1928-1932 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Millais, Mrs. John G., 1931-1932 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Milliken, William M., 1928-1930 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Mills, Ogden., 1925-1929 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Milton, Robert, Inc., 1925-1927 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Moline, Adah., 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Montross, N. E., 1923-1928 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Moore, E. C., Jr., 1926-1932 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Morehead, John M., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Morey, C. R., 1919-1932 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Morgan Guide., 1925 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Morgan, H. S., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Morgan, J. D., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Morgan, J. Pierpont., 1920-1928 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Morgan, Junius, S., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Morgan Wing at MMA (With Ref. to "Morgan Handbook"), 1929-1930 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Morisini, Giulia P. -- Bequest., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Morris, Miss Frances., 1922-1929 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Mosan Enamels, Article On., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Musical Instruments., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Muhsam Glass (Duplicates of Letters)., 1927 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Myers, George Hewitt., 1927-1930 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - M -- Miscellaneous (Ma-Me)., 1918-1933 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - M -- Miscellaneous (Mi-My)., 1918-1933 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Near Eastern Art (Collection of)., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - New York Society of Craftsman., 1922-1929 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - New York Historical Society., 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - New York University., 1923-1930 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Niver, Charles., 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Norton, Charles (& Mrs.)., 1922 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Norton, Mrs. Eliot., 1920 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - N -- Miscellaneous., 1919-1933 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Olmsted, Anna W., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Osborn, William Church., 1921-1933 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - O -- Miscellaneous., 1921-1932 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Paff, Merriman (Durlacher)., 1925-1927 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Partridge, Frank, Inc., 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Paulsson, Dr. Gregor (Swedish Exhibition)., 1927-1930 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Persian Art., 1930-1931 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Persian Art., 1932 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Peruvian Textiles, Book on., 1930 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Phillips, John G., 1930-1933 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Picture Book -- Italian Renaissance Sculpture., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Picture Book -- Leaves & Flowers in Tapestries., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Pillsbury, Arthur., 1922-1930 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Pintadoes, Article On., 1928 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Plaisted, George E., 1919-1920 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Planiscig, Dr. Leo., 1928-1933 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Plimpton, Russell A., 1918-1929 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham., 1923-1932 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Pope, Office of John Russell & Memoranda Regarding New Addition., 1930-1932 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Porter, A. Kingsley (Mr. & Mrs.)., 1921-1933 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Porter, Mrs. Harold E., 1933 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Postcards., Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Post, Professor Chandler R., 1922-1929 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Post, Mrs. Edward C., 1930-1951 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Post Office Receipt., 1928 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Post Office Regulations., 1925 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Pratt, C. J., 1929-1932 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Pratt, George D., 1922-1933 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Price, F. Newlin (Ferargil Galleries)., 1922-1933 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Priest, Alan R., 1920-1932 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Private Secretaties., Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Purchases., 1922 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Purchases., 1923 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Purchases of Mr. Breck in Europe., 1924 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Purchases of Mr. Breck in Europe., 1925 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Purchases of Mr. Breck in Europe., 1932 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - P -- Miscellaneous (Pa-Pe)., 1919-1933 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - P -- Miscellaneous (Ph-Py)., 1923-1933 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Q -- Miscellaneous., Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Raymond & Whitcomb Co., 1930 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Receipts for Registered or Insured Mail., 1922-1925 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1925 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1926 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1927 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1928 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1929 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Records of Letters Referred to Other Members of Museum Staff., 1933 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reitz, S. C. Bosch., 1924-1930 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reitz, S. C. Bosch., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Remington, Preston., 1924-1933 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Repairs, Recommendations For., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Repairs, Recommendations For., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Requests for Information., 1917-1918 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Requests for Information., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Requests for Information., 1920 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Requests for Information., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Requests for Information., 1922-1923 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Requests for Information., 1923 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Requests for Information (A-J)., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Requests for Information (K-Z)., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Requests for Information (A-J)., 1925 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Requests for Information (K-Z)., 1925 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Requests for Information (A-K)., 1926 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Requests for Information (L-Z)., 1925-1926 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Information., 1927 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Requests for Information (A-K)., 1927-1928 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Requests for Information (L-Z)., 1928 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Requests for Information (A-K)., 1929 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Requests for Information (L-Z)., 1929 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Requests for Information (A-J)., 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Requests for Information (K-Z)., 1930 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Requests for Information., 1930-1931 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Information (A-G)., 1932 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Requests for Information (H-M)., 1932 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Requests for Information (N-Z)., 1932 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Requests for Information (A-G)., 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Requests for Information (H-M)., 1933 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Requests for Information (N-Z)., 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Requests for Material for Lectures -- (Letters from Mr. Kent)., 1923 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Requests for Material for Lectures -- (Letters from Mr. Kent)., 1924 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Requests for Material for Lectures -- (Letters from Mr. Kent)., 1925 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Restaurant., 1922-1924 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Restaurant., 1925-1926 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Reyburn, Samuel W. (Lord & Taylor)., 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Richards, Professor Charles R., 1924-1932 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Richter, Gisella M. A., 1924-1932 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Robineau, Adelaide Alsop., 1922-1928 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Robineau Memorial Exhibition., 1929 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1919-1921 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1924 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1925 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1926 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1927 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1928 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1929 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Robinson, Edward., 1930-1931 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Rogers, Margaret (Miss)., 1923-1924 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence with Joseph Breck)., 1918-1930 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, A-F)., 1918-1923 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, G-H)., 1921-1923 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, I-L)., 1918-1923 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, M-O)., 1919-1923 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, P-R)., 1919-1923 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, S)., 1921-1923 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Correspondence of, T-Z)., 1919-1923 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. (Drawings of)., Undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Roosval, Professor Johnny., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Rorimer, James J., 1927-1933 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Rugs (Classification, Collections, Repairs)., 1922-1930 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ryan, John Barry., 1932 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - R -- Miscellaneous (Ra-Ri)., 1918-1933 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - R -- Miscellaneous (Ro-Ry)., 1918-1932 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Sachs, Mrs. Howard J. (Eleanor)., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Sachs, Professor Paul J. (Fogg Art Museum)., 1923-1932 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Sage Fund Income for Installation -- American Wing., 1924 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Homer., 1924-1930 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Samplers Exhibition., 1930 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Sangiorgi Gallery., 1918 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Santarelli, Mrs. B. M. C., 1924 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Saxe, Miss Eleanor B., 1924 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Scherer, Margaret., 1926-1932 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Schiff, Ida (Collection of Laces)., 1920 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Schiff, Mortimer., 1928-1929 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Scholle, Hardinge., 1921-1929 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Schwaiger, Imre., 1929-1931 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Seager Bequest., 1925-1926 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Seligmann, Andre., 1923 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Seligmann, Arnold., 1923 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Seligman, (Arnold) Rey & Co. Inc., 1924-1926 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Seligman, (Arnold) Rey & Co. Inc., 1927-1929 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Seligmann, (Arnold) Rey & Co., Inc., 1930-1931 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Seligmann, (Arnold) Rey & Co., Inc., 1932-1933 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Seligmann, Arnold Rey & Co., Inc. (Louis XV Room -- Photos, Plans)., 1932 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Seligmann, Jacques., 1922 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Seligmann, Jacquest & Co., 1925-1930 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Seligmann, Jacquest & Fils., 1929 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sestieri's Gallery., 1921-1930 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Shapley, John., 1923-1929 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Smith-Clifford, H., 1932-1933 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Solon, Leon V., 1925-1930 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Soren, T. H., 1926-1951 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Spanish Art Galleries., 1918-1923 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Stark, Harold., 1925-1929 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Stenographers (Applicants)., 1929 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Stenographers -- Applicants, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Stillman, Dr. E. G., 1922 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Stillwell, John E. (Dr.)., 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Straus, Herbert, Jesse, Percy (RH Macy & Co.)., 1922-1933 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sweden (Crown Prince)., 1926 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Swedish Exhibition -- Handbook & Memoranda., 1926-1927 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Symons, Henry & Co., Inc., 1925-1932 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - S -- Miscellaneous (Sa-Sh)., 1919-1933 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - S -- Miscellaneous (Si-Sy)., 1919-1933 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Taylor, Francis Henry., 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Textiles., Undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Frederick F. (Mary Clark Thompson Bequest)., 1919-1924 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Tiffany Studios., 1925-1930 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Todd, John R. (Todd Robertson, Todd Engineering Corporation)., 1932 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Tomitch, Dr. D., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Townsend, Gertrude., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Transfers., 1928 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Transfers., 1933 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Troyes, Some Sculpture of the School of (Article On)., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - T -- Miscellaneous., 1918-1933 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Upton, Joseph M., 1929-1933 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - U -- Miscellaneous., 1925-1933 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Vacation Data., 1922 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Vacation Data., 1923 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Vacation Data., 1924 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Vacation Data., 1925 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Vacation Data., 1926 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Vacation Data., 1927-1928 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Vacation Data., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Vacation Data., 1930 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Vacation Data., 1931 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Vacation Data., 1932 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Vacation Data., 1933 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Vacations., 1934-1936 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Van Derlip, R., 1918-1919 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Vargis Bust ("Aviation")., 1932-1933 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Vasselot, Monsieur J. J. Marquet De., 1925-1931 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Venetian Room., 1925 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Vigoroux -- Demotte Case., 1924 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - V -- Miscellaneous., 1919-1933 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Wallpapers (List)., 1924 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Walters, Henry., 1919-1930 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Wanamaker, John., 1918-1926 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Wearne, Harry., 1922-1929 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Wehle, Harry B., 1925-1930 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Weil, Milton., 1928-1932 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Wellesley, Lord Gerald., 1931 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - White, Allom & Co., 1922-1931 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Whiting, Frederic Allen (Cleveland Museum of Art)., 1918-1925 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Wiener Werkstaette of America., 1923-1928 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Wiener, P. Lester (Contempora, Inc.)., 1929 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Wildenstein & Co., 1923-1926 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Wildenstein, Felix., 1919 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Winlock, H. E., 1930-1932 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Winlock, H. E., 1933 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Winthrop, Grenville L., 1924-1929 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Woodworth, Ralph., 1929 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - W -- Miscellaneous., 1919-1933 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Zorach, Marguerite (Mrs. William)., 1922-1923 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Zuckerman, Miss B., 1922-1933 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - X-Y-Z -- Miscellaneous., 1919-1932 (Box 29, Folder 22)